<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
 <id>io.github.GnomeMpv.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
 <name>GNOME MPV</name>
 <summary>GTK+ frontend for mpv</summary>
 <translation type="gettext">gnome-mpv</translation>
 <description>
  <p>GNOME MPV is a simple GTK+ frontend for mpv, which is a very powerful media player capable of playing virtually all video and audio formats. The design of GNOME MPV is based on GNOME HIG, though it is not dependent on any GNOME libraries. GNOME MPV also offers an option to disable client-side decorations (CSD) for better compatibility with non-GNOME systems.</p>
  <p xml:lang="ca">El GNOME MPV és un frontal senzill per a l’MPV, un reproductor multimèdia capaç de reproduir qualsevol format d’àudio i vídeo. S’ha dissenyat el GNOME MPV amb les directrius d’interfícies del GNOME, però no hi té cap dependència. El GNOME MPV també ofereix un paràmetre per inhabilitar la decoració del client (CSD) i millorar la compatibilitat amb altres sistemes diferents del GNOME.</p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">GNOME MPV je jednoduché rozhraní vytvořené v GTK+ pro mpv, což je velice schopný přehrávač, který dokáže přehrát prakticky jakýkoliv formát videa i zvuku. Vzhled GNOME MPV se zakládá na konvencích GNOME, ale přitom na žádných knihovnách GNOME nezávisí. Navíc GNOME MPV umožňuje vypnout okenní dekorace na straně klienta (CSD), aby lépe zapadal do jiných prostředí.</p>
  <p xml:lang="de_DE">GNOME MPV ist eine einfache auf GTK+ basierende Oberfläche für den mpv Mediaplayer. Mittels mpv können so gut wie alle Video- und Audioformate abgespielt werden. GNOME MPV ist gemäß der GNOME HIG gestaltet, hat jedoch keine Abhängigkeiten zu GNOME-Bibliotheken. Weiterhin kann die CSD-Titelleiste für bessere Integration in Nicht-GNOME-Systeme deaktiviert werden.</p>
  <p xml:lang="hu">A GNOME MPV egy egyszerű GTK+ felület az mpv-hez, egy rendkívül erőteljes médialejátszóhoz, amely gyakorlatilag az összes videó- és hangformátum lejátszására képes. A GNOME MPV dizájnja a GNOME HIG-en alapszik, habár nem függ egyetlen GNOME könyvtártól sem. A GNOME MPV továbbá lehetővé teszi a kliensoldali díszítések letiltását a GNOME-tól eltérő rendszerekkel való jobb kompatibilitás érdekében.</p>
  <p xml:lang="it">GNOME MPV è un semplice frontend in GTK+ per MPV, un potente media player capace di riprodurre potenzialmente ogni tipo di formato audio e video. Il design di GNOME MPV è basato sulle HIG di GNOME, tuttavia non dipende da nessuna delle sue librerie. GNOME MPV offre anche un'opzione per disattivare le decorazioni client-side (CSD) per una migliore compatibilità con i sistemi che non usano GNOME.</p>
  <p xml:lang="nl">GNOME MPV is een simpele GTK+ frontend voor mpv, wat een erg krachtige mediaspeler is die eigenlijk alle video en audio formaten kan afspelen. Het design van GNOME MPV is gebaseerd op GNOME HIG, maar het gebruikt geen GNOME bibliotheken. GNOME MPV heeft ook een optie om client-side decoraties (CSD) uit te zetten voor betere compatibiliteit met niet-GNOME systemen</p>
  <p xml:lang="pl">GNOME MPV jest prostym interfejsem GTK+ programu mpv - potężnego odtwarzacza obsługującego wszystkie formaty nagrań dźwięku i wideo.  Projekt interfejsu jest zgodny z wytycznymi GNOME HIG, choć sam program nie jest zależy od bibliotek GNOME. GNOME MPV umożliwia wyłączenie wyświetlania obramowań po stronie klienta (CDS) dla lepszej integracji z systemami bez środowiska GNOME.</p>
  <p xml:lang="pt_PT">GNOME MPV é um interface simples em GTK+ para mpv, que é um poderoso reprodutor multimédia capaz de reproduzir praticamente todos os formatos de vídeo e áudio. O projeto do GNOME MPV é baseada em GNOME HIG, embora não seja dependente de todas as bibliotecas do GNOME. GNOME MPV também oferece uma opção para desativar decorações do lado do cliente (CSD) para melhor compatibilidade com os sistemas não-GNOME.</p>
  <p xml:lang="ru">GNOME MPV - это простая GTK+ оболочка для MPV, поэтому является очень мощным медиаплеером, который способен воспроизводить практически все видео и аудио форматы. Дизайн GNOME MPV соответствует GNOME HIG. GNOME MPV также предлагает опцию, чтобы отключить декорирование на стороне клиента (CSD) для лучшей совместимости с системами, отличными от GNOME.</p>
  <p xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME MPV 是一个简单的 GTK+ mpv 前端，mpv 是一个功能强大的媒体播放器，可用于播放几乎所有的视频和音频格式。尽管该程序不依赖于任何 GNOME 库，GNOME MPV 是一个基于 GNOME HIG（人机界面准则）设计的程序。GNOME MPV 还提供禁用客户端装饰（CSD）的选项以为不运行 GNOME 的系统提供更好的兼容性。</p>
  <p xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME MPV 是一個簡單的 GTK+ mpv 前端，mpv 是一個功能強大的媒體播放器，可用於播放幾乎所有的視訊和音訊格式。儘管該程式不依賴於任何 GNOME 庫，GNOME MPV 是一個基於 GNOME HIG（人機介面準則）設計的程式。GNOME MPV 還提供禁用客戶端裝飾（CSD）的選項以為不執行 GNOME 的系統提供更好的相容性。</p>
  <p>Features:</p>
  <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">Nabízí:</p>
  <p xml:lang="de_DE">Funktionen:</p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités</p>
  <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
  <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
  <p xml:lang="nl">Functies:</p>
  <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
  <p xml:lang="pt_PT">Características:</p>
  <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
  <p xml:lang="zh_CN">特性：</p>
  <p xml:lang="zh_TW">特性：</p>
  <ul>
   <li>Drag and drop playlist</li>
   <li xml:lang="ca">La llista de reproducció es pot reorganitzar amb la tècnica d’arrossegar i deixar anar</li>
   <li xml:lang="cs">Seznam přehrávání („playlist“) s možností přetáhnout soubory myší</li>
   <li xml:lang="de_DE">Wiedergabeliste mit Drag and Drop-Unterstützung</li>
   <li xml:lang="hu">Fogd és vidd lejátszási lista</li>
   <li xml:lang="it">Drag and drop della playlist</li>
   <li xml:lang="pl">lista odtwarzania obsługująca przeciąganie plików,</li>
   <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Arrastar e soltar lista de reprodução</li>
   <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка Drag'n'Drop</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_CN">拖放播放列表</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_TW">拖放播放列表</li>
   <li>Loading external mpv configuration files</li>
   <li xml:lang="ca">Càrrega de fitxers de configuració externs de l’MPV</li>
   <li xml:lang="cs">Načítání externího konfiguračního souboru pro mpv</li>
   <li xml:lang="de_DE">Laden externer mpv-Konfigurationsdateien</li>
   <li xml:lang="hu">Külső mpv konfigurációs fájlok betöltése</li>
   <li xml:lang="it">Carica un file di configurazione di MPV esterno</li>
   <li xml:lang="nl">Externe mpv configuratiebestanden laden</li>
   <li xml:lang="pl">wczytywanie zewnętrznych plików konfiguracyjnych programu mpv,</li>
   <li xml:lang="pt_PT">A carregar ficheiros de configuração mpv externos</li>
   <li xml:lang="ru">Загрузка внешних конфигурационных файлов MPV</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_CN">正在载入外部 mpv 配置文件</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_TW">正在載入外部 mpv 配置檔</li>
   <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interface</li>
   <li xml:lang="ca">Interfície per a MPRIS2 del D-Bus</li>
   <li xml:lang="cs">Rozhraní MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
   <li xml:lang="de_DE">MPRIS2 D-Bus Schnittstelle</li>
   <li xml:lang="hu">MPRIS2 D-Bus interfész</li>
   <li xml:lang="it">Interfaccia MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
   <li xml:lang="pl">obsluga interfejsu D-Bus MPRIS2.</li>
   <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Interface MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
   <li xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_CN">MPRIS2 D-Bus 界面</li>
   <li xml:lang="zh_TW">MPRIS2 D-Bus 介面</li>
  </ul>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-0.png</image>
   <caption>The main window showing the application in action</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal en funcionament</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno a aplikace v akci</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenser von GNOME MPV</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="hu">Az alkalmazás működés közben</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale in funzione</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster dat de applicatie in actie laat zien</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno przedstawiające działanie programu</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal mostra a aplicação em ação</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно, показывающее приложение в действии</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">显示运行中应用的主窗口</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">顯示執行中套用的主視窗</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
   <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-1.png</image>
   <caption>The main window with CSD disabled</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal amb la CSD inhabilitada</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno s vypnutými dekoracemi na straně klienta</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenster ohne CSD-Titelleiste</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="hu">A főablak letiltott díszítésekkel</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale con le decorazioni client-side disattivate</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met CSD uitgeschakeld</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pl">Głowne okno programu z wyłączonym obramowaniem po stronie klienta</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com CSD desativada</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с отключённым CSD</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">关闭了 CSD 的主窗口</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">關閉了 CSD 的主視窗</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
   <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-2.png</image>
   <caption>The main window with playlist open</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal amb la llista de reproducció oberta</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno s otevřeným seznamem přehrávání</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenster mit Wiedergabeliste</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="hu">A főablak megnyitott lejátszási listával</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale con la playlist visualizzata</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met een afspeellijst open</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno programu z listą odtwarzania</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com lista de reprodução aberta</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с открытым списком воспроизведения</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">打开了播放列表的主窗口</caption>
   <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">打開了播放列表的主視窗</caption>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">http://gnome-mpv.github.io</url>
 <url type="bugtracker">http://github.com/gnome-mpv/gnome-mpv/issues</url>
 <update_contact>gnome-mpv_at_openmailbox.org</update_contact>
</component>