<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
 <id>mate-screenshot.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
 <name>MATE Screenshot</name>
 <summary>A screenshot utility for MATE Desktop</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ar">أداة التقاط صورة الشاشة لسطح مكتب متّة</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="be">Утыліта здымання экрану асяроддзя MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за заснемане на екрана на MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="br">Ur maveg da bakañ skrammadoù evit burev MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ca">Una utilitat de captura de pantalla per a l'escriptori MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Una utilitat de captura de pantalla per a l'escriptori MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="cs">Zachycení snímku obrazovky pro MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="da">Et skærmbilledredskab for MATE-skrivebordet</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug zur Anfertigung von Bildschirmfotos für die MATE-Arbeitsumgebung</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="el">Μιαεφαρμογή για λήψη στιγμιοτύπου οθόνης για το MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="en_AU">A screenshot utility for MATE Desktop</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="en_GB">A screenshot utility for MATE Desktop</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="es">Una utilidad de captura de pantalla para el escritorio MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="et">Ekraanitõmmise võtmise vahend MATE töölauale</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="fi">Kuvakaappausohjelma MATE Työpöydälle</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="fr">Un utilitaire de capture d'écran pour le bureau MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="hu">Képernyőkép készítő segédprogram a MATE asztali környezethez</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="hy">Էկրանի նկարի օժանդակ ծրագիր MATE Աշխատանքային սեղանի համար</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="id">Utilitas screenshot Desktop MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="it">Un'applicazione per screenshot per l'ambiente desktop MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ja">MATE デスクトップのスクリーンショットユーティリティー</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="kk">MATE жұмыс үстелі үшін скриншот утилитасы</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ko">마테 데스크톱용 화면 촬영 도구</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="lt">Ekrano kopijų paslaugų programa MATE darbalaukiui</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ms">Utiliti cekupan skrin untuk Desktop MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="nb">Et skjermbilderedskap for MATE-skrivebordet</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="nl">Een schermafdruk-hulpprogramma voor de MATE-werkomgeving</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie zrzutów ekranu dla środowiska MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="pt">Um utilitário de captura de ecrã para o Ambiente de Trabalho MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Um utilitário de captura de tela para o Ambiente de Trabalho MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ro">O unealtă pentru capturi de ecran pentru desktopul MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ru">Утилита для создания снимков экрана для рабочего стола MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na tvorbu snímok obrazovky prostredia MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="sl">Orodje za zajem zaslonskih slik v MATE Namizju</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="sr">Помагало за снимање екрана за Мејтову радну површ</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett skärmbildsverktyg för MATE Skrivbord</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="th">ความสามารถในการถ่ายภาพหน้าจอสำหรับเดสก์ท็อปของ MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="tr">MATE Masaüstü için ekran fotoğrafı programı</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб створення знятків екрану для середовища MATE</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">MATE 桌面的截屏工具</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">適用於 MATE 桌面環境的螢幕截圖工具</summary>
 <description><p> MATE Screenshot is a simple utility that lets you capture screenshots of your desktop or of application windows. You can select to copy them to the system clipboard or save them in Portable Network Graphics (.png) image format. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ar">ملتقط متّة لصور الشاشة أداة بسيطة تسمح لك بالتقاط صور لسطح مكتبك أو نافذة تطبيقك. تستطيع نسخها إلى الحافظة أو حفظها إلى صورة بصيغة رسوميات الشبكة المحمولة (.png).</description>
 <description xml:lang="be"><p> Здымак экрану MATE - гэта простая ўтыліта, што дазваляе атрымліваць здымкі таго, што адбываецца ў вас на стале або ў пэўным акне. Можна капіяваць выніковыя здымкі ў буфер абмену ці захоўваць у фармаце Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="bg"><p> MATE Снимка на екрана е прост инструмент, който ви позволява да направите снимки на работния ви екран или на прозорците на приложенията ви. Можете да изберете да ги копирате в клипборда или да ги запазите във графичен формат .png (Portable Network Graphics). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="br"><p> Pakerez skrammadoù MATE a dalv d'ur maveg da bakañ srammadoù diwar ho purev pe diwar prenestroù hoc'h arloadoù. Mar fell deoc'h e vezont eilet e-barzh golver ar reizhiad pe enrollet dre ar mentrezh skeudennoù Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ca"><p> La captura de pantalla de MATE és una utilitat senzilla que us permet fer captures de pantalla del vostre escriptori o de les finestres de les aplicacions. Podeu seleccionar copiar-les al porta-retalls del sistema o desar-les amb el format d'imatge «Portable Network Graphics» (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ca@valencia"><p> La captura de pantalla del MATE és una utilitat senzilla que us permet fer captures de pantalla del vostre escriptori o de les finestres de les aplicacions. Podeu seleccionar copiar-les al porta-retalls del sistema o guardar-les amb el format d'imatge «Portable Network Graphics» (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="cs"><p> Zachycení snímku obrazovky pro MATE je jednoduchý nástroj umožňující vám zachytit snímek vaší pracovní plochy či oken aplikace. Můžete zvolit jeho zkopírování do schránky či jej uložit ve formátu Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="da"><p> MATE Screenshot er et simpelt redskab hvor du kan tage skærmbilleder af dit skrivebord eller af programvinduet. Du kan vælge at kopiere dem til systemets udklipsholder eller gemme dem i Portable Network Graphics (.png)-billedformatet. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="de"><p> MATE-Bildschirmfoto ist ein einfaches Werkzeug, mit dem man Bildschirmfotos des Schreibtischs oder von Programmfenstern anfertigen kann. Man kann auswählen, ob sie in die Zwischenablage kopiert oder im portablen Netzwerkgrafikbildformat (.png) gespeichert werden sollen.</p></description>
 <description xml:lang="en_AU"><p> MATE Screenshot is a simple utility that lets you capture screenshots of your desktop or of application windows. You can select to copy them to the system clipboard or save them in Portable Network Graphics (.png) image format. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="en_GB"><p> MATE Screenshot is a simple utility that lets you capture screenshots of your desktop or of application windows. You can select to copy them to the system clipboard or save them in Portable Network Graphics (.png) image format. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="es"><p> MATE Screenshot es una utilidad simple que le permite tomar capturas de pantalla de su escritorio o de las ventanas de la aplicación. Puede seleccionar para copiarlos al portapapeles del sistema o guardarlos en el formato de imagen Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="et"><p> MATE Kuvatõmmis on lihtne utiliit töölauast või rakenduste akendest kuvatõmmiste võtmiseks. Tõmmiseid on võimalik kopeerida süsteemi lõikelauale või salvestada PNG (Portable Network Graphics) pildivormingusse. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Capture d'écran MATE est un petit utilitaire vous permettant d'effectuer des captures d'écran de votre bureau et des fenêtres des applications. Vous pouvez choisir de les copier dans le presse-papier ou de les sauvegarder dans un fichier image au format Portable Network Graphics (.png).</p></description>
 <description xml:lang="hu"><p>A MATE Screenshot egy egyszerű segédprogram az asztal vagy egy alkalmazás ablakának „fotózásához”. Az elkészült képernyőkép bemásolható a rendszer vágólapjára, vagy Portable Network Graphics (.png) kép formátumban elmenthető. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="hy"><p> MATE էկրանային պատկերը պարզ օժանդակ ծրագիր է, որը թույլ է տալիս լուսանկարել էկրանի կադրը աշխատասեղանի կամ ծրագրերի պատուհանների։ Դուք կարող եք ընտրել պատճենել դրանք փոխանակման բուֆերում կամ պահպանել դրանք Portable Network Graphics մեջ (.png) պատկերի ձևաչափով։ </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="id"><p> MATE Screenshot adalah utilitas yang mampu menangkap screenshot dari desktop atau jendela aplikasi Anda. Anda bisa memilih untuk menyalin pada clipboard sistem atau menyimpannya pada format Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="it"><p> MATE Screenshot è una semplice applicazione che ti permette di catturare screenshot del tuo desktop o della finestra di un'applicazione. Puoi copiarli nei tuoi appunti o salvarli nel formato Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ja"><p>MATE スクリーンショットはデスクトップやアプリケーションのスクリーンショットを撮影するためのシンプルなユーティリティです。スクリーンショットをクリップボードにコピーしたり、Portable Network Graphics (.png) 形式で保存することができます。</p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ko"><p> 마테 스크린샷은 바탕 화면 또는 응용 프로그램 창의 화면을 캡처할 수있는 간단한 유틸리티입니다. 선택해서 시스템 클립보드에 복사하고 이동식 네트워크 그래픽 이미지 형식(.png) 으로 저장할 수 있습니다. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="lt"><p> MATE Screenshot yra paprasta programa, kuri leidžia padaryti darbalaukio arba langų ekrano kopijas. Jas galite nukopijuoti į sistemos iškarpinę arba įrašyti PNG (.png) formatu. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ms"><p> Cekupan Skrin MATE merupakan utiliti ringkas yang  membolehkan anda tangkap cekupan skrin dekstop anda atau tetingkap aplikasi. Anda boleh memilih salinannya ke papan keratan sistem atau simpan dalam format imej Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="nb"><p> MATE-skjermskudd er et simpelt redskap for å ta skjermbilder av ditt skrivebord eller programvindu. Du kan velge å kopiere dem til systemets utklippstavle eller lagre dem i Portable Network Graphics (.png) billedformat. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="nl"><p> MATE Schermafdruk is een eenvoudig hulpprogramma waarmee u schermafdrukken van uw bureaublad of van toepassingsvensters kunt maken. U kunt ervoor kiezen om ze te kopiëren naar het klembord of om ze op te slaan in de afbeeldingssoort Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="pl"><p> Mate Screenshot jest prostym narzędziem, które pozwala na przechwytywanie zrzutów ekranu pulpitu lub okna aplikacji. Możesz wybrać, aby skopiować je do schowka systemowego lub zapisać je w formacie graficznym Portable Network Graphics (.png) </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="pt"><p> O Mate Screenshot é uma simples ferramenta que te permite capturar uma imagem da tua área de trabalho ou de uma aplicação. Tu podes selecionar para copiar a imagem para a área de transferência ou guarda-la em formato PNG (Portable Network Graphics). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p> A Captura de Tela MATE é um utilitário simples que permite capturar imagens da sua área de trabalho ou de janelas de aplicativos. Você pode copiar estas imagens para a área de transferência ou salvá-las em arquivos no formato PNG. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ro"><p> Captură de ecran MATE este un utilitar simplu care vă permite să capturați imagini ale desktop-ului sau ale ferestrelor aplicațiilor. Puteți alege să le copiați în memoria clipboard a sistemului sau să le salvați în formatul Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="ru"><p> Снимки экрана MATE – это простое приложение, которое помогает делать снимки всего экрана или окон приложений. Вы можете выбрать копирование снимков в системный буфер обмена или сохранить их в формате Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="sk"><p> MATE Screenshot je jednoduchým nástrojom, pomocou ktorého viete vytvoriť snímky vašej obrazovky, alebo daných okien. Môžete zvoliť ich skopírovanie do schránky systému, alebo ich môžete uložiť do obrázkového formátu Portable Network Graphics (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="sr"><p> Мејтов снимач екрана је једноставно помагало које вам омогућава да направите снимак екрана ваше радне површи или прозора програма. Можете изабрати да их умножите у оставу система или да их сачувате у запису слике Преносне мрежне графике (.png). </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="sv"><p> MATE Skärmbild är ett enkelt verktyg som låter dig fånga skärmbilder av ditt skrivbord eller av programfönster. Du kan välja att kopiera dem till systemets klippbord eller spara dem i Portable Network Graphics (.png) bildformat. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="th"><p> โปรแกรมจับภาพหน้าจอของ MATE เป็นโปรแกรมอรรถประโยชน์อย่างง่ายที่ให้คุณจับภาพหน้าจอของเดสก์ท็อปของคุณ หรือของหน้าต่างโปรแกรมก็ได้ คุณสามารถเลือกที่จะคัดลอกพวกมันไปไว้ที่คลิปบอร์ดของระบบ หรือบันทึกพวกมันในรูปแบบของภาพแบบ Portable Network Graphics (.png) </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="tr"><p> MATE Ekran Fotoğrafı masaüstünüzün ya da uygulama pencerelerinin fotoğrafını çekmenize imkân sağlayan sade bir programdır. Fotoğrafları sistem panosuna kopyalamayı ya da Taşınabilir Ağ Grafiği (Portable Network Graphics, .png) biçiminde kaydetmeyi seçebilirsiniz. </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="uk"><p> MATE Screenshot це простий засіб, що дозволяє робити знятки усієї стільниці або вікна застосунку. Ви можете вибрати копіювання їх у буфер обміну чи зберігання їх у форматі зображення Portable Network Graphics (.png) . </p></description>
 <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p> MATE 截图工具是一个用于捕捉桌面或窗口截图的简易实用工具。你可以选择将截图添加到系统剪贴板或将其保存为可移动网络图形 (.png) 图像格式。</p></description>
 <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p> MATE 螢幕截圖是一個讓您可以擷取您的桌面或是應用程式視窗截圖的簡單小工具。您可以選取以將它們複製到系統剪貼簿中或是將它們儲存為可攜式網路圖形 (.png) 圖片格式。 </p></description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image width="800" height="450">
    https://alexpl.fedorapeople.org/AppData/mate-screenshot/screens/mate-screenshot_01.png
   </image>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">http://www.mate-desktop.org</url>
 <updatecontact>mate-dev@ml.mate-desktop.org</updatecontact>
 <project_group>MATE</project_group>
</component>