<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>

  <enum id="org.gnome.metacity.MetaPlacementMode">
    <value value="0" nick="smart"/>
    <value value="1" nick="cascade"/>
    <value value="2" nick="center"/>
    <value value="3" nick="origin"/>
    <value value="4" nick="random"/>
  </enum>

  <schema path="/org/gnome/metacity/" id="org.gnome.metacity" gettext-domain="@GETTEXT_PACKAGE@">
    <key type="b" name="compositing-manager">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Compositing Manager</summary>
      <description>Determines whether Metacity is a compositing manager.</description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="reduced-resources">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>If true, trade off usability for less resource usage</summary>
      <description>If true, Metacity will give the user less feedback by using wireframes, avoiding animations, or other means. This is a significant reduction in usability for many users, but may allow legacy applications to continue working, and may also be a useful tradeoff for terminal servers. However, the wireframe feature is disabled when accessibility is on.</description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="edge-tiling">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Enable edge tiling when dropping windows on screen edges</summary>
      <description>If enabled, dropping windows on vertical screen edges maximizes them vertically and resizes them horizontally to cover half of the available area. Dropping windows on the top screen edge maximizes them completely.</description>
    </key>
    <key name="placement-mode" enum="org.gnome.metacity.MetaPlacementMode">
      <default>'smart'</default>
      <summary>Window placement behavior</summary>
      <description>Metacity's default window-placement behavior is smart (first-fit), similar to behaviors in some other window managers. It will try to tile windows so that they do not overlap. Set this option to "smart" for this behavior. This option can be set to "center" to place new windows in the centers of their workspaces, "origin" for the upper-left corners of the workspaces, or "random" to place new windows at random locations within their workspaces.</description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="alt-tab-thumbnails">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Show window content thumbnail in Alt-Tab</summary>
      <description>If set to true, Metacity will show window content thumbnails in the Alt-Tab window instead of only icons.</description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="theme">
      <default>'Adwaita'</default>
      <summary>Current theme</summary>
      <description>The theme determines the appearance of window borders, titlebar, and so forth.</description>
    </key>
  </schema>

  <schema path="/org/gnome/metacity/keybindings/" id="org.gnome.metacity.keybindings">
    <key type="as" name="toggle-tiled-left">
      <default><![CDATA[['<Super>Left']]]></default>
    </key>
    <key type="as" name="toggle-tiled-right">
      <default><![CDATA[['<Super>Right']]]></default>
    </key>
  </schema>

</schemalist>