<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>eom.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="af">MATE se Oog</name>
  <name xml:lang="am">የ ሜት አይን</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">عين متّة</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn">জিনোমের চোখ</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn_IN">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="br">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="cmn">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="cy">EOM ('Eye of MATE)</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Mates øje</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="dz">ཨའི་ཨོཕ་ཇི་ནོམ།</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Μάτι του MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_AU">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_CA">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Eye of MATE (gnoomi silm)</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">MATEren begia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">چشم گنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">MATEn silmä</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Ollo do MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="gu">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">העין של MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">गनोम की आँख</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="hy">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Eye of MATE myndasskoðun</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">გნომის თვალი </name>
  <name xml:lang="kab">Tiṭ n MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">MATE көзі</name>
  <name xml:lang="kn">ಐ ಆಫ್  MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">마테의 눈</name>
  <name xml:lang="ks">गनोमच अच्छ</name>
  <name xml:lang="ku">Çavê MATE'yê</name>
  <name xml:lang="ku_IQ">چاوی MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ky">MATE көзү</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="mai">गनोम क' आँखि</name>
  <name xml:lang="mg">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="mk">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഗ്നോം മിഴി</name>
  <name xml:lang="mr">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">MATE को आँखा</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Oog van Mate (Eye of Mate)</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="nso">Leihlo la MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="or">ନୋମର ଆଖି</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਦੀ ਅੱਖ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="pms">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ps">د جنومي سترګه</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Visualizador de Imagens</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Глаз MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="si">MATE ඇස</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Oko MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Мејтово око</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Oči Gnoma</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">ஐ ஆப் க்னோம்</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">MATE'nin Gözü</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Око MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="uz">MATE'ning koʻzi</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Mắt MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="wa">Eye of Mate</name>
  <name xml:lang="xh">Iliso le-MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">MATE 之眼</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Eye of MATE</name>
  <name xml:lang="zu">Iso le MATE</name>
  <summary>Simple image viewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="am">ቀላል የ ምስል መመልከቻ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">عارض صور بسيط</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Просты прагляднік выяў</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Опростен преглед на изображения</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="br">Ur welerez skeudennoù eeun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Visualitzador simple d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Visualitzador simple d'imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Jednoduchý prohlížeč obrázků</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Simpel billedfremviser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Einfaches Bildbetrachtungsprogramm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Απλό πρόγραμμα προβολής φωτογραφιών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_AU">Simple image viewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Simple image viewer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Visor de imágenes simple</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Lihtne pildinäitaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Irudi-ikusle sinplea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Yksinkertainen kuvankatseluohjelma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Simple visionneuse d'images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Visor de imaxes sinxelo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Jednostavni preglednik slika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Egyszerű képmegjelenítő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hy">Պարզ պատկեր դիտող</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Viewer citra sederhana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Einfaldur myndaskoðari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Semplice visualizzatore di immagini</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">簡潔な画像ビューア</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Суреттерді қарапайым көрсетушісі</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">간단한 그림 보기 프로그램</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Paprasta paveikslų žiūryklė</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Pelihat imej ringkas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Enkel bildeviser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Simpele afbeeldingskijker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Prosta przeglądarka obrazów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pms">Sempi visualisator d’imagin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Visualizador simples de imagens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Visualizador de imagens simples</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Vizualizator simplu de imagini</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Простой просмотрщик изображений</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduchý prehliadač obrázkov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Preprost pregledovalnik slik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sq">Shikues figurash i thjeshtë</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Једноставан прегледач слика</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Enkel bildvisare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมแสดงรูปอย่างง่าย</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sade bir resim görüntüleyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Простий перелядач зображень</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uz">Sodda rasm ko'ruvchi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Trình xem ảnh ơn giản</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">简单的图像查看器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">簡單的圖片檢視器</summary>
  <description><p> Eye of MATE is a simple viewer for browsing images on your computer. Once an image is loaded, you can zoom and rotate the image, and also view subsequent images in the directory the image was loaded from. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="am"><p> የ ሜት አይን ቀላል የ ምስል መመልከቻ ነው በ እርስዎ ኮምፒዩተር ውስጥ: አንድ ጊዜ ምስል ከ ተጫነ: እርስዎ ምስል ማሳየት እና ማዞር ይችላሉ: እና እንዲሁምተከታታይ ምስል ከ ዳይሬክቶሪ ውስጥ መመልከት ይችላሉ: ከ </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="be"><p> Eye of MATE - гэта просты прагляднік выяў на вашым камп'ютары. Дазваляе набліжаць, аддаляць і паварочваць выявы, а таксама глядзець наступныя і папярэднія выявы з таго ж каталогу. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="bg"><p> Eye of MATE е опростена програма за преглед на изображения. Когато изображението е заредено, можете да го приближите или въртите и да преглеждате други изображения от същата директория. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="br"><p> Eye of MATE a dalv d'ur welerez da vereiñ e-touez ar skeudennoù war hoc'h urzhiataer. Ur wech ma'z eo bet karget ar skeudenn e c'hallit zoumañ pe c'hwelañ ar skeudenn ha gwelet e vez ivez ar skeudennoù all war-he-lec'h en teuliad ma 'z eo bet karget ar skeudenn dioutañ. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ca"><p> Eye of MATE és un visualitzador simple per navegar per les imatges a l'ordinador. Un cop que es carrega una imatge, podeu fer zoom a la imatge i rotar-la, i també veure les imatges posteriors al directori des d'on es va carregar la imatge. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ca@valencia"><p> L'Eye of MATE és un visualitzador simple per a navegar per les imatges a l'ordinador. Una vegada es carrega una imatge, podeu fer zoom a la imatge i girar-la, i també veure les imatges posteriors al directori des d'on es va carregar la imatge. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="cs"><p>Eye of MATE je jednoduchý prohlížeč obrázků pro desktopové prostředí MATE. Umožňuje jednoduché úpravy obrázků - přibližování, otáčení. Umí procházet i další obrázky v adresáři.</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="da"><p>Eye of MATE er en simpel fremviser til at gennemse billeder på din computer. Når er billede er indlæst, så kan du zoome og rotere billedet, og også se efterfølgende billeder i mappen billedet blev indlæst fra. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="de"><p>Eye of MATE ist ein einfaches Betrachtungsprogramm, mit dem Bilder auf dem Rechner durchsucht werden können. Sobald ein Bild geladen ist, kann es vergrößert und gedreht werden. Außerdem können die nachfolgenden Bilder des Verzeichnisses, aus dem es geladen wurde, betrachtet werden</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="el"><p>Το Eye of MATE είναι ένα απλό πρόγραμμα προβολής και περιήγησης φωτογραφιών στον υπολογιστή σας. Κάθε φωτογραφία που θα φορτώσετε μπορείτε να την μεγεθύνετε, να την περιστρέψετε και επίσης, να δείτε επόμενες φωτογραφίες του φάκελου από τον οποίο φορτώθηκε η πρώτη φωτογραφία.</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="en_AU"><p> Eye of MATE is a simple viewer for browsing images on your computer. Once an image is loaded, you can zoom and rotate the image, and also view subsequent images in the directory the image was loaded from. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="en_GB"><p> Eye of MATE is a simple viewer for browsing images on your computer. Once an image is loaded, you can zoom and rotate the image, and also view subsequent images in the directory the image was loaded from. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="es"><p> Eye of MATE es un simple visor para visualizar imágenes en su equipo. Una vez cargada la imagen, puede ampliar y rotar la imagen, y también ver las imágenes siguientes en el directorio del que la imagen fue cargada. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="et"><p> Eye of MATE on lihtne vahend pildifailide näitamiseks. Näitamiseks laaditud pilti on võimalik suurendada ja pöörata, samuti saab pildikataloogi esitada slaidiseansina. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="eu">MATE-ren begia ikusle sinple bat da gainbegiratu zure ordenagailuko irudietarako. Behin irudi bat kargatuta, zarata atera dezakezu eta irudia txandakatu eta ondoko irudiak ikusi direktorioan ere irudia kargatu zen.</description>
  <description xml:lang="fi">MATEn silmä on yksinkertainen kuvakatselin tietokoneesi kuvien selaukseen. Kun kuva on ladattu, voit lähentää ja kiertää kuvaa ja voit myös katsella seuraavia kuvia ladatun kuvan hakemistossa.</description>
  <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Eye of MATE est une simple visionneuse pour parcourir les images sur votre ordinateur. Lorsqu'une image est affichée, vous pouvez zoomer et faire pivoter l'image, et voir également les images suivantes contenues dans le même dossier.</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="gl"><p> Ollo do MATE é un visor sinxelo para navegar polas imaxes no seu equipo. Unha vez cargada a imaxe, pode ampliala ou rotala, pode tamén ver as imaxes seguintes no directorio do que foi cargada a imaxe. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="hu"><p> Az Eye of MATE egy egyszerű képnézegető program. A kép betöltésekor az nagyítható és forgatható, és a képet tartalmazó könyvtár képi is megnézhetőek. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="hy"><p> Eye of MATE֊ը պարզ արտապատկերող միջոց է ձեր համակարգչի վրա գտնվող պատկերների դիտելու համար</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="id"><p> Eye of MATE adalah viewer sederhana untuk menjelajahi citra pada komputer Anda. Setelah citra ditampilkan, Anda bisa zoom dan merotasi citra, dan juga menampilkan citra berikutnya pada direktori dimana citra tersebut berada. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="it"><p> Eye of MATE è un semplice visualizzatore per navigare immagini sul tuo computer. Una volta che l'immagine è stata caricata, puoi zoomarla e ruotarla, e anche vedere le immagini seguenti nella cartella da cui era stata caricata. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ja"><p> Eye of MATE はコンピューター内の画像を閲覧するためのシンプルなビューアーです。拡大縮小や回転、画像と同じフォルダー内に存在する画像の閲覧などが可能です。</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="kk"><p> MATE көзі - бұл компьютеріңіздегі суреттерді шолуға арналған қарапайым қолданба. Сурет жүктелгеннен кейін оның масштабын және бұрылуын өзгерте аласыз, және сурет алынған бумада орналасқан басқа да суреттерді көре аласыз. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ko"><p> 마테의 눈은 컴퓨터의 그림을 찾다보는 간단한 그림 보기 프로그램입니다. 그림을 불러오면 그림을 확대, 축소, 회전할 수 있으며, 그림을 불러온 디렉터리의 각각의 여러가지 그림도 살펴볼 수 있습니다. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="lt"><p> Eye of MATE yra paprasta paveikslų žiūryklė, skirta naršyti po paveikslus jūsų kompiuteryje. Kai įkeliamas paveikslas, galite ji didinti/mažinti, pasukti, o taip pat žiūrėti kitus paveikslus esančius tame pačiame, įkelto paveikslo, kataloge. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ms"><p> Eye of MATE merupakan pelihat ringkas untuk melayari imej dalam komputer anda. Bila imehj dimuatkan, anda boleh zum dan putar imej, dan juga dapat melihat imej berikutnya di dalam direktori imej yang dimuatkan. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="nb"><p>Eye of MATE er en enkel fremviser for å se igjennom bilder på din datamaskin. Når et bilde er lastet inn, kan du forstørre og rotere bildet, og også se påfølgende bilder i mappen bildet ble lastet inn fra. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="nl"><p>Oog van Mate (Eye of Mate) is een simpele kijker voor het verkennen van afbeeldingen op uw computer. Als een afbeelding eenmaal is geladen, kunt u de afbeelding vergroten, verkleinen en draaien.  Daarnaast kunt u de overige afbeeldingen bekijken die zich bevinden in de map  waaruit u de huidige afbeelding heeft gekozen.</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="pl"><p> Eye of MATE jest prostą przeglądarką obrazów na twoim komputerze. Po załadowaniu obrazu, możesz powiększać i obracać obraz, jak również wyświetlać kolejne obrazy w katalogu, w którym obraz jest załadowany. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="pt"><p> Eye of MATE é um visualizador simples para navegar imagens no seu computador. Quando uma imagem é carregada, pode ampliar e rodar a imagem, e também ver imagens subsequentes na pasta de onde a imagem foi carregada. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="ru"><p> Глаз MATE – это простой просмотрщик изображений на вашем компьютере. После загрузки изображения его можно увеличить или уменьшить, а также просматривать следующие изображения в каталоге, с которого изображение было загружено. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="sk"><p> Eye of MATE je jednoduchý prehliadač obrázkov na vašom počítači. Zobrazené obrázky si môžete priblížiť, otočiť, alebo prezrieť aj ďalšie obrázky z priečinka, z ktorého bol prvý obrázok načítaný. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="sr"><p> Мејтово око је једноставан прегледач за разгледање слика на вашем рачунару. Када учитате слику, можете да је повећате и окренете, и такође да видите слике подскупа у директоријуму из ког је учитана слика. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="sv"><p> Eye of MATE är en enkel visare för att bläddra bilder på datorn. Efter att en bild laddats, kan du zooma och rotera bilden, och även visa efterföljande bilder i katalogen bilden laddades från. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="tr"><p> MATE'nin gözü, bilgisayarınızdaki resimleri taramak için kullanabileceğiniz sade bir görüntüleyicidir. Herhangi bir resim yüklendiğinde onu döndürebilir, yakınlaştırabilir ve dosyanın yüklendiği klasördeki diğer resimleri görüntüleyebilirsiniz. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="uk"><p> Око MATE це простий переглядач зображень на екрані Вашого комп’ютера. Після завантаження зображення його можна збільшити або зменшити, а також переглядати наступні зображення у каталозі з якого зображення було завантажено. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="vi"><p> Mắt Mate là một trình xem ảnh đơn giản để duyệt hình ảnh trên máy tính của máy tính của bạn. Một khi một hình ảnh đã được nạp, bạn có thể zoom và xoay ảnh, và cũng có thể xem các hình ảnh khác trong thư mục hình ảnh đã được nạp từ. </p></description>
  <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p> MATE 之眼是一个简易的图像浏览器。图像完全载入后，你可以缩放和旋转图像，也可以显示存放于某个目录中的图像序列。</p></description>
  <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p> Eye of MATE 是一個可以讓您在您的電腦上瀏覽圖片的簡單檢視器。只要圖片一載入，您就可以縮放或旋轉圖片，也可以檢視圖片所在的資料夾中的其他圖片。 </p></description>
  <url type="homepage">http://mate-desktop.org/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">http://mate-desktop.org/gallery/1.8/eom.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>