<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2015-2019 gnome-mpv -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>io.github.GnomeMpv.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_PT">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="de_DE">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">GNOME MPV</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">GNOME MPV</name>
  <summary>GTK+ frontend for mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">MPV 之 GTK 前端程式</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">MPV 的 GTK+ 前端程序</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">GTK+ gränssnitt för mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">GTK+ pročelje za mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">GTK+ прочеље за mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">GTK+ интерфейс для MPV</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_PT">Interface GTK+ para mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wykorzystuje interfejs GTK do obsługi programu MPV</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">GTK+ frontend voor mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">MPVのGTKフロントエンド</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un frontend in GTK+ per MPV</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">GTK+ felület az mpv-hez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">GTK+ prednji program za mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interface en GTK+ pour mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz GTK+ para MPV</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de_DE">Eine GTK-Oberfläche für den Medienspieler mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">GTK+-frontend til mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">GTK+ rozhraní nad mpv</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Interfície GTK+ per a l'MPV</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">GTK+ интерфейс за MPV</summary>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.GnomeMpv.desktop</launchable>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-mpv</translation>
  <description>
    <p>
   GNOME MPV is a simple GTK+ frontend for mpv, which is a very powerful media
   player capable of playing virtually all video and audio formats. The design
   of GNOME MPV is based on GNOME HIG, though it is not dependent on any GNOME
   libraries. GNOME MPV also offers an option to disable client-side decorations
   (CSD) for better compatibility with non-GNOME systems.
  </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME MPV 是一個簡單的 GTK+ mpv 前端，mpv 是一個功能強大的媒體播放器，可用於播放幾乎所有的視訊和音訊格式。儘管該程式不依賴於任何 GNOME 庫，GNOME MPV 是一個基於 GNOME HIG（人機介面準則）設計的程式。GNOME MPV 還提供禁用客戶端裝飾（CSD）的選項以為不執行 GNOME 的系統提供更好的相容性。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME MPV 是一个简单的 GTK+ mpv 前端，mpv 是一个功能强大的媒体播放器，可用于播放几乎所有的视频和音频格式。尽管该程序不依赖于任何 GNOME 库，GNOME MPV 是一个基于 GNOME HIG（人机界面准则）设计的程序。GNOME MPV 还提供禁用客户端装饰（CSD）的选项以为不运行 GNOME 的系统提供更好的兼容性。</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">GNOME MPV är ett enkelt GTK+ drivet gränssnitt för mpv, som är en väldigt kraftfull mediaspelare kapabel att spela upp i princip alla video och ljud format. Utformningen av GNOME MPV är baserat på GNOME HIG, dock är det inte beroende av några GNOME bibliotek. GNOME MPV erbjuder även som alternativ att inaktivera fönsterdekorationer i klienten (CSD) för bättre kompatibilitet med icke-GNOME system. </p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">GNOME MPV je jednostavno GTK+ pročelje za mpv, koji je veoma moćan prikazivač sposoban da pusti praktično sve video i audio formate. Dizajn GNOME MPV-a je baziran na GNOME HIG, ali je nezavistan od bilo koje GNOME biblioteke. GNOME MPV takođe nudi opciju onemogućavanja dekoracija klijenta (CSD) zbog kompatibilnosti s drugim okruženjima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">GNOME MPV је једноставно GTK+ прочеље за mpv, који је веома моћан приказивач способан да пусти практично све видео и аудио формате. Дизајн GNOME MPV-а је базиран на GNOME HIG, али је независтан од било које GNOME библиотеке. GNOME MPV такође нуди опцију онемогућавања декорација клијента (CSD) због компатибилности с другим окружењима.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">GNOME MPV - это простая GTK+ оболочка для MPV, поэтому является очень мощным медиаплеером, который способен воспроизводить практически все видео и аудио форматы. Дизайн GNOME MPV соответствует GNOME HIG. GNOME MPV также предлагает опцию, чтобы отключить декорирование на стороне клиента (CSD) для лучшей совместимости с системами, отличными от GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">GNOME MPV é um interface simples em GTK+ para mpv, que é um poderoso reprodutor multimédia capaz de reproduzir praticamente todos os formatos de vídeo e áudio. O projeto do GNOME MPV é baseada em GNOME HIG, embora não seja dependente de todas as bibliotecas do GNOME. GNOME MPV também oferece uma opção para desativar decorações do lado do cliente (CSD) para melhor compatibilidade com os sistemas não-GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">GNOME MPV jest prostym interfejsem GTK+ programu mpv - potężnego odtwarzacza obsługującego wszystkie formaty nagrań dźwięku i wideo.  Projekt interfejsu jest zgodny z wytycznymi GNOME HIG, choć sam program nie jest zależy od bibliotek GNOME. GNOME MPV umożliwia wyłączenie wyświetlania obramowań po stronie klienta (CDS) dla lepszej integracji z systemami bez środowiska GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">GNOME MPV is een simpele GTK+ frontend voor mpv, wat een erg krachtige mediaspeler is die eigenlijk alle video en audio formaten kan afspelen. Het design van GNOME MPV is gebaseerd op GNOME HIG, maar het gebruikt geen GNOME bibliotheken. GNOME MPV heeft ook een optie om client-side decoraties (CSD) uit te zetten voor betere compatibiliteit met niet-GNOME systemen</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">GNOME MPV è un semplice frontend in GTK+ per MPV, un potente media player capace di riprodurre potenzialmente ogni tipo di formato audio e video. Il design di GNOME MPV è basato sulle HIG di GNOME, tuttavia non dipende da nessuna delle sue librerie. GNOME MPV offre anche un'opzione per disattivare le decorazioni client-side (CSD) per una migliore compatibilità con i sistemi che non usano GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A GNOME MPV egy egyszerű GTK+ felület az mpv-hez, egy rendkívül erőteljes médialejátszóhoz, amely gyakorlatilag az összes videó- és hangformátum lejátszására képes. A GNOME MPV dizájnja a GNOME HIG-en alapszik, habár nem függ egyetlen GNOME könyvtártól sem. A GNOME MPV továbbá lehetővé teszi a kliensoldali díszítések letiltását a GNOME-tól eltérő rendszerekkel való jobb kompatibilitás érdekében.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">GNOME MPV est une simple interface GTK+ pour mpv, qui est un lecteur multimédia très puissant capable de lire pratiquement tous les formats vidéo et audio. La conception de GNOME MPV est basée sur GNOME HIG, bien qu'elle ne dépende d'aucune bibliothèque GNOME. GNOME MPV offre également la possibilité de désactiver les décorations côté client (CSD) pour une meilleure compatibilité avec les systèmes non GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">GNOME MPV es un interfaz GTK+ simple para MPV, un reproductor multimedia capaz de reproducir cualquier formato de video y audio. El diseño de GNOME MPV se basa en las directrices de interfaz de GNOME, aunque no depende de sus bibliotecas. GNOME MPV también ofrece una opción para desactivar las decoraciones del lado del cliente (CSD) para una mejor compatibilidad con otros escritorios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de_DE">GNOME MPV ist eine einfache auf GTK+ basierende Oberfläche für den mpv Mediaplayer. Mittels mpv können so gut wie alle Video- und Audioformate abgespielt werden. GNOME MPV ist gemäß der GNOME HIG gestaltet, hat jedoch keine Abhängigkeiten zu GNOME-Bibliotheken. Weiterhin kann die CSD-Titelleiste für bessere Integration in Nicht-GNOME-Systeme deaktiviert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">GNOME MPV er en simpel GTK+-frontend til mpv, som er en meget kraftful medieafspiller som er i stand til at afspille stort set alle video- og lydformater. GNOME MPVs design er baseret på GNOME HIG, med det afhænger ikke af nogen GNOME-biblioteker. GNOME MPV tilbyder også en valgmulighed til at deaktivere klientsidedekorationer (CSD) for bedre kompatibilitet med systemer som ikke er GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">GNOME MPV je jednoduché rozhraní vytvořené v GTK+ pro mpv, což je velice schopný přehrávač, který dokáže přehrát prakticky jakýkoliv formát videa i zvuku. Vzhled GNOME MPV se zakládá na konvencích GNOME, ale přitom na žádných knihovnách GNOME nezávisí. Navíc GNOME MPV umožňuje vypnout okenní dekorace na straně klienta (CSD), aby lépe zapadal do jiných prostředí.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El GNOME MPV és una interfície GTK + simple per a l'MPV, un reproductor multimèdia capaç de reproduir qualsevol format de vídeo i àudio. El disseny del GNOME MPV es basa en les directrius d'interfície del GNOME, tot i que no hi té cap dependència. El GNOME MPV també ofereix una opció per desactivar les decoracions del client (CSD) per millorar compatibilitat amb altres escriptoris.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">GNOME MPV е опростен GTK+ интерфейс за MPV, който е мощен мултимедиен плеър, способен да възпрозвежда множество мултимедийни формати. Дизайна на GNOME MPV съответства GNOME HIG. GNOME MPV също предлага опция, която изключва Gnome 3 декорацията на прозорецa (CSD) за по- добра съвместимост с графични среди, различни от GNOME.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">特性：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">特性：</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Functies:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Značajke:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de_DE">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktionaliteter:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Nabízí:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Опции:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Drag and drop playlist</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">拖放播放列表</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">拖放播放列表</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Dra och släpp spellista</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Prevuci i otpusti listu puštanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Превуци и отпусти листу пуштања</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка Drag'n'Drop</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Arrastar e soltar lista de reprodução</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">lista odtwarzania obsługująca przeciąganie plików,</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Drag and drop della playlist</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Fogd és vidd lejátszási lista</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Povuci i ispusti popis izvođenja</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Glisser-déposer la liste de lecture</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Arrastrar y soltar las entradas de la lista de reproducción</li>
      <li xml:lang="de_DE">Wiedergabeliste mit Drag and Drop-Unterstützung</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Træk og slip spilleliste</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Seznam přehrávání („playlist“) s možností přetáhnout soubory myší</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Es poden arrossegar i deixar anar les entrades de la llista de reproducció</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Поддръжка на Drag'n'Drop</li>
      <li>Loading external mpv configuration files</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">正在載入外部 mpv 配置檔</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">正在载入外部 mpv 配置文件</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Läser in externa mpv konfigurationsfiler</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">Učitavam spoljne mpv konfiguracione datoteke</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Учитавам спољне mpv конфигурационе датотеке</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Загрузка внешних конфигурационных файлов MPV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">A carregar ficheiros de configuração mpv externos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">wczytywanie zewnętrznych plików konfiguracyjnych programu mpv,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Externe mpv configuratiebestanden laden</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Carica un file di configurazione esterno di mpv</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Külső mpv konfigurációs fájlok betöltése</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">Učitavanje vanjske mpv datoteke podešavanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Chargement des fichiers de configuration externes pour mpv</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Carga de archivos de configuración externos de MPV</li>
      <li xml:lang="de_DE">Laden externer mpv-Konfigurationsdateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Indlæser eksterne mpv-konfigurationsfiler</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Načítání externího konfiguračního souboru pro mpv</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Càrrega de fitxers de configuració externs de l'MPV</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Зареждане на външни MPV конфигурационни файлове</li>
      <li>MPRIS2 D-Bus interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_TW">MPRIS2 D-Bus 介面</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">MPRIS2 D-Bus 接口</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">MPRIS2 D-Bus gränssnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr@latin">MPRIS2 D-Bus sučelje</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">MPRIS2 D-Bus сучеље</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Interface MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">obsluga interfejsu D-Bus MPRIS2.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Interfaccia MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">MPRIS2 D-Bus interfész</li>
      <li xml:lang="hr">MPRIS2 D-Bus sučelje</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Interface D-Bus MPRIS2</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Interfaz de D-Bus MPRIS2</li>
      <li xml:lang="de_DE">MPRIS2 D-Bus Schnittstelle</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">MPRIS2 D-Bus-grænseflade</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Rozhraní MPRIS2 D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Interfície de D-Bus MPRIS2</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">MPRIS2 D-Bus интерфейс</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-01-21" version="0.16">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <ul>
          <li>
       Split up the General tab in the preferences dialog
     </li>
          <li>
       Improve behavior when toggling playlist under tiling window managers
     </li>
          <li>
       Move app menu items to primary menu
     </li>
          <li>
       Use separate MPRIS DBus connection for each window
     </li>
          <li>
       Add support for MPRIS property LoopStatus
     </li>
          <li>
       Add option --mpv-options for setting arbitrary mpv options from the
       command-line
     </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-09-08" version="0.15">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Set default screenshot directory to XDG_PICTURES_DIR
     </li>
          <li>
      Improve handling of --window-scale, --autofit,
      --autofit-larger, and --autofit-smaller
     </li>
          <li>
      Add command line option for setting WM_ROLE
     </li>
          <li>
      Add context menu item for removing playlist items
     </li>
          <li>
      Add context menu item for copying location of playlist items
     </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-02-17" version="0.14">
      <description>
        <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
        <ul>
          <li>
      Add option to make skip buttons change playlist entries rather than
      chapters
     </li>
          <li>
      Make the file chooser accept non-local locations
     </li>
          <li>
      Add right-click menu entry for looping a single file
     </li>
          <li>
      Handle property change events for fullscreen and window-scale
     </li>
          <li>
      Add option to autohide mouse cursor in windowed mode
     </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-10-13" version="0.13"/>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-0.png</image>
      <caption>The main window showing the application in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">顯示執行中套用的主視窗</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">显示运行中应用的主窗口</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно, показывающее приложение в действии</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal mostra a aplicação em ação</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno przedstawiające działanie programu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster dat de applicatie in actie laat zien</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale in funzione</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Az alkalmazás működés közben</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Glavni prozor prikazuje aplikaciju u akciji</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale montrant l'application en action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal con la aplicación en acción</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenser von GNOME MPV</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Hovedvinduet som viser programmet i funktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno a aplikace v akci</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal amb l'aplicació en acció</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Основният прозорец показва програмата в действие</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-1.png</image>
      <caption>The main window with CSD disabled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">關閉了 CSD 的主視窗</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">关闭了 CSD 的主窗口</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret med CSD inaktiverat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Glavni prozor sa onemogućenim CSD-om</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Главни прозор са онемогућеним CSD-ом</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с отключённым CSD</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com CSD desativada</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Głowne okno programu z wyłączonym obramowaniem po stronie klienta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met CSD uitgeschakeld</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale con le decorazioni client-side disattivate</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A főablak letiltott díszítésekkel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Glavni prozor s onemogućenim CSD-om</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale avec CSD désactivé</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal con las decoraciones del lado del cliente deactivadas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenster ohne CSD-Titelleiste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Hovedvinduet med deaktiveret skærmdisplay</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno s vypnutými dekoracemi na straně klienta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal amb les decoracions del client desactivades</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Главният прозорец с изключен CSD</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://gnome-mpv.github.io/images/screenshot-2.png</image>
      <caption>The main window with playlist open</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">打開了播放列表的主視窗</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">打开了播放列表的主窗口</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret med spellista öppen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Glavni prozor sa otvorenom listom puštanja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Главни прозор са отвореном листом пуштања</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Главное окно с открытым списком воспроизведения</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_PT">Janela principal com lista de reprodução aberta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Janela principal com a lista de reprodução aberta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno programu z listą odtwarzania</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster met een afspeellijst open</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale con la playlist visualizzata</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A főablak megnyitott lejátszási listával</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Glavni prozor sa otvorenim popisom izvođenja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale avec la liste de lecture ouverte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal con la lista de reproducción abierta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de_DE">Das Hauptfenster mit Wiedergabeliste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Hovedvinduet med åben spilleliste</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní okno s otevřeným seznamem přehrávání</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal amb la llista de reproducció oberta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Главният прозорец с отворен спъсък за изпълнение</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://gnome-mpv.github.io</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://github.com/gnome-mpv/gnome-mpv/issues</url>
  <update_contact>gnome-mpv_at_teknik.io</update_contact>
</component>
